<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sightseeing</string>
    <string name="category_events">Events</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_accommodation">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="episcopal_castle_desc">The Haapsalu Bishop’s Castle and Cathedral, which was
        established in the 13th century as the centre of the Saare-Lääne Diocese, is one of the
        best preserved castles in Estonia. Visit the museum complex in the convent building where
        you will find exhibition halls with finds from the castle and mysterious vaulted cellars.
        Rent an audio guide for tour commentary in six languages.
        \nInteresting facts:
        \n* You might encounter Estonia’s most famous ghost – the White Lady.
        \n* In the moat, you will find a stylized medieval children’s playground, a large
        chessboard, archery grounds and clay workshop.
        \n* Climb the 38-metre-high bell tower and at noon listen to the carillon that is heard
        throughout the city.
        \n* In the summer, take advantage of the busy events calendar.</string>
    <string name="episcopal_castle">Episcopal Castle</string>
    <string name="tchaikovsky_bench">Tchaikovsky\'s Bench</string>
    <string name="tchaikovsky_bench_desc">The world-famous Russian composer Pjotr Tchaikovsky s
        tayed in Haapsalu in 1867. To commemorate him, a memorial bench was erected on the
        Šokolaadi Promenaad, where the maestro loved to watch the sunrise from the shore and
        marvel the swans. Interesting to know: in Haapsalu, Tchaikovsky continued to work on his
        opera \"Voevoda\" and composed the cycle of piano pieces \"Souvenir de Hapsal\". After
        having heard the Estonian folk song \"Dear Mary\", he later used the melody in his famous
        VI Symphony, the first notes of the tune were also carved into the dolomite memorial bench.
        Today, the bench is equipped with a technical solution with the aid of which you can listen
        to the composer\'s music and information related to him.</string>
    <string name="maria_magdaleena_church">Maria-Magdaleena Church</string>
    <string name="maria_magdaleena_church_desc">The Estonian Orthodox Maria Magdaleena Church is
        located in an idyllic area of Haapsalu – on the Promenade. Russian Tsar Alexander II
        attended the opening of the church in 1852.
        \nThe church was restored to its present state only a few years ago. The church is open on
        Sundays from 9 am to noon. To visit at other times, please contact us in advance.
        Interesting fact: The church and the surrounding buildings are depicted in Ilon Wikland’s
        book Long, Long Journey. Ilon Wikland, who was the illustrator of Astrid Lindgren’s books,
        describes her Haapsalu childhood in the book.</string>
    <string name="railway_station">Haapsalu Railway Station</string>
    <string name="railway_station_desc">This resort town was a favourite summer spot of Russian
        tzars. The railway station was built according to original drawings; the complex consists
        of four parts: passenger terminal, imperial pavilion, a sheltered passage linking those,
        and a unique covered platform that is 213.6 m long.
        \nGood to know: the Russian Tzar himself was in favour of the idea to build this station
        and supported the construction. The first passenger train arrived in Haapsalu in 1904;
        the last one left in 1995. Take advantage of a unique opportunity to travel from Haapsalu
        to Riisipere (50 km) by bike – the old railway bed has been turned into Lääne County health trail.
        \nToday, there is a bus stop in front of the railway station.
        \nIt belongs in the National Register of Cultural Monuments.</string>
    <string name="ungru_manor">Ungru manor</string>
    <string name="ungru_manor_desc">The ruins of the Ungru manor used to represent one of the most
        impressive Neo-Baroque buildings in Estonia, although it never was really finished. Its
        sophisticated footprint and the numerous baroque volute ornaments on its gables are
        characteristic for the castle.
        \nInteresting to know: The Ungru Manor was an almost exact copy of the Merseburg castle in
        Germany. After World War II the manor fell into the hands of Soviet troops, in 1968 the
        chief of the airport decided to use the ruins of the manor to fill in the holes in the
        runway. About one third of the manor was torn down, fortunately the rest was preserved
        until today. Compare the neat ruins of the manor to the contrasting Soviet airfield remains
        next to them</string>
    <string name="sun_dial">Haapsalu Sundial</string>
    <string name="sun_dial_desc">There is sundial designed by artist Roman Haavamäe on the Haapsalu
        seaside Promenade. The face of the dial depicts the life of man – starting with a child and
        ending with an old man supported by a cane. On the Promenade also admire the decorative
        dolomite stairways and decorative columns by the same artist, as well as the ornamented
        stairs on both sides of the Assembly Hall. Interesting fact: The sundial shows the local
        sun time, which is about 90 slower than daylight savings time. Go and check to see if your
        watch is correct.</string>
    <string name="epp_maria">Epp Maria Gallery</string>
    <string name="epp_maria_desc">The creative work of Epp Maria Kokamägi, one of Estonia\’s most
        famous artists, includes oil paintings, watercolours, book design and theatre and film
        design. The building, which was built as a café during Estonia\'s first period of
        independence, now houses a gallery over two floors, where exhibitions change according to
        the seasons. In addition to Epp Maria\'s wonderful paintings, you can also enjoy the
        paintings and furniture created by her husband Jaak Arro, the ceramics of Liisu Arro and
        the paintings of Imbi Lind.</string>
    <string name="old_town">Old Town</string>
    <string name="old_town_desc">Haapsalu, which is bordered by the sea on three sides, fits on a
        piece of land with a size of just 10.59 km2. The Old Town is located on a peninsula with
        two eskers, which continue to the north-west as a chain of islets (holms) connected to the
        mainland. There are low meanders between the holms – Suur and Väike Viik.
        \nThe culturally and environmentally valuable Old Town of Haapsalu can be divided into its
        medieval section and the 20th century health resort area. The medieval part is around the
        Episcopal castle, with the medieval network of Kooli, Jaani, Vee, Linda, Rüütli and V
        äike-Mere Streets and buildings. It is surrounded by a belt of wooden houses and the
        Promenade, Aafrika beach and parks.</string>
    <string name="bird_tower">Gulf Tagalaht and Birdwatching Tower</string>
    <string name="bird_tower_desc">For most of the year the Gulf Tagalaht in Haapsalu is an
        exciting place for birdwatching. There is no need to leave town, simply visit the 15-metre
        high birdwatching tower on the Promenade. When visiting the tower you will get a full
        overview of birdlife in the area between Haapsalu and Noarootsi. When the ice breaks in
        April and May, the gulf is filled with swans and different types of ducks. In autumn – in
        September and October – it is interesting to witness the departure of geese and cranes.</string>
    <string name="beach_promenade">Africa Beach and Promenade</string>
    <string name="beach_promenade_desc">The splendour of Haapsalu, the famous Czarist era resort,
        is recalled by the seafront Promenade and its jewel - the Assembly Hall with its wooden
        “gingerbread”. Walk on the sloping promenade and glance dreamily at the sea; check the time
        at the sundial and have a rest on the bench named for the world-famous composer Tchaikovsky.
        nInteresting facts: The Promenade starts at the exotically named Africa Beach, and ends at
        the Chocolate Promenade, which is named after a former café. There is a children’s
        playground on the Promenade and the town’s only observation tower. There is also a monument
        to Carl Hunnius, the discoverer of Haapsalu’s therapeutic mud behind the band shell.</string>
    <string name="museum_night">Museum Night</string>
    <string name="museum_date">20.05</string>
    <string name="kuursaal_opening">Kuursaal\'s season opening party</string>
    <string name="kuursaal_date">20.05</string>
    <string name="graphic_design">Graphical design festival</string>
    <string name="graphic_date">27.05 – 25.06</string>
    <string name="fairy_tale_conference">Fairy tale conference</string>
    <string name="fairy_tale_date">1.06</string>
    <string name="italy_wine">Italy\'s wine days</string>
    <string name="wine_date">2.06 – 3.06</string>
    <string name="al_bano">Al Bano Carrisi concert</string>
    <string name="al_bano_date">3.06</string>
    <string name="flag_day">Estonian flag day</string>
    <string name="flag_day_date">4.06</string>
    <string name="kreeg_days">Nargenfestival Kreeg\'s days</string>
    <string name="kreeg_days_date">10.06 – 11.06</string>
    <string name="vaiko_elite">Night concert Vaiko Eplik and the ELIIT</string>
    <string name="vaiko_elite_date">15.06</string>
    <string name="midsummer_festival">Midsummer fire festival</string>
    <string name="midsummer_date">23.06 – 24.06</string>
    <string name="tchaikovsky_haapsalu">Tchaikovsky\'s Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="tchaikovsky_haapsalu_date">28.06 – 1.07</string>
    <string name="vanamuusika">Old Music festival</string>
    <string name="old_music_date">5.07 – 9.07</string>
    <string name="summer_play">Summer Play</string>
    <string name="summer_play_date">5.07 – 23.07</string>
    <string name="regatta">Muhu Gulf\'s Regatta</string>
    <string name="regatta_date">7.07</string>
    <string name="beauty_car_show">American Beauty Car Show</string>
    <string name="beauty_car_show_date">14.07 – 16.07</string>
    <string name="yoga_festival">Yoga festival</string>
    <string name="yoga_festival_date">21.07 – 23.07</string>
    <string name="rock_haapsalu">Rock in Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="rock_haapsalu_date">28.07 – 29.07</string>
    <string name="august_blues">August Blues</string>
    <string name="august_blues_date">4.08 – 6.08</string>
    <string name="white_lady">Time of The White Lady</string>
    <string name="white_lady_date">11.08 – 13.08</string>
    <string name="accordion_festival">Accordion festival</string>
    <string name="accordion_festival_date">12.08</string>
    <string name="lade_day">Lace day</string>
    <string name="lace_day_date">13.08</string>
    <string name="taste_promenade">The Promenade of Tastes</string>
    <string name="taste_promenade_date">19.08</string>
    <string name="belinda">Belinda Carlisle and Shanon</string>
    <string name="belinda_date">19.08</string>
    <string name="nostalgia">Nostalgia Days</string>
    <string name="nostalgia_date">8.09 – 10.09</string>
    <string name="margot">Greek restaurant Margot Food and Style</string>
    <string name="margot_address">Posti tänav 37, Haapsalu 90502 | (+372) 473 5003</string>
    <string name="fra_mare_restaurant">Fra Mare restaurant \"Bergfeldt\"</string>
    <string name="fra_mare_address">Ranna tee 2, Haapsalu 90403 | (+372) 472 4605</string>
    <string name="dietrich">Cafe Hapsal Dietrich</string>
    <string name="dietrich_address">Karja tänav 10, Haapsalu 90503 | (+372) 509 4549</string>
    <string name="fast_rabbitt">Restaurant Fast Rabbit</string>
    <string name="fast_rabbit_address">Karja tänav 5, Haapsalu 90502 | (+372) 510 5396</string>
    <string name="bakery">Müüriääre Bakery</string>
    <string name="bakery_address">Karja tänav 7, Haapsalu 90502 | (+372) 506 0924</string>
    <string name="grande">Pizza Grande</string>
    <string name="grande_address">Karja tn 6, Haapsalu 90503 | (+372) 473 7200</string>
    <string name="taksi_pub">Taksi Pub</string>
    <string name="taksi_pub_address">Posti tänav 29, Haapsalu 90502 | (+372) 504 7428</string>
    <string name="talumehe">Talumehe Tavern</string>
    <string name="talumehe_address">Karja tn 2, Haapsalu 90503 | (+372) 530 62755</string>
    <string name="fra_mare_spa">Fra Mare Thalasso SPA</string>
    <string name="fra_mare_spa_address">Ranna tee 2, Haapsalu | (+372) 472 4600</string>
    <string name="sunset_dream">Sunset Dream Apartment</string>
    <string name="sunset_dream_address">Suur-Liiva tänav 15, Haapsalu | (+372) 604 2204</string>
    <string name="baltic_hotel">Baltic Hotel Promenaadi</string>
    <string name="baltic_hotel_address">Sadama tänav 22, Haapsalu | (+372) 473 7250</string>
    <string name="marienholm">Marienholm Villa</string>
    <string name="marienholm_address">Väike-Viigi tänav 10, Haapsalu | (+372) 563 91671</string>
    <string name="hotel_day_villa">Hotel Päeva Villa</string>
    <string name="hotel_day_vill_address">Lai tänav 7, Haapsalu | (+372) 534 88222</string>
    <string name="reta_house">Reta\'s House Accommodation</string>
    <string name="reta_house_address">Posti tänav 25, Haapsalu | (+372) 566 87802</string>
    <string name="supeluse">Supeluse Guesthouse</string>
    <string name="supeluse_address">Supeluse tänav 4, Haapsalu | (+372) 564 66880</string>
    <string name="attractionimage">AttractionImage</string>
    <string name="episcopal_castle_maps">Lossiplats tn 3, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="tchaikovsky_maps">P. Tshaikovski puiestee, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="magdaleena_maps">Rüütli tn 2, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="railway_maps">Raudtee tänav 2, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="ungru_maps">Ungru Loss, Kiltsi küla, Ridala vald, Lääne maakond</string>
    <string name="sun_dial_maps">Promenaadi tn, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="epp_maria_maps">Kalda tänav 2, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="old_town_maps">Karja tn, Haapsalu</string>
    <string name="bird_maps">Promenaadi tn 3, Haapsalu 90502</string>
    <string name="promenade_maps">Promenaadi tänav, Haapsalu</string>

</resources>
